yo what's up hi can i do a freestyle rap
for you guys yeah sure
that was amazing
that was weird sound oh my god yo what's
up
hi how's it going i'm gonna tell you i'm
wonderful i'm so good i'm so good thank
you for asking can i do a freestyle rap
for you guys yeah yeah sure so so can
you all give me like three
challenging words to inspire my
freestyle
oh god um
bad bet is great but like give me like a
challenging word
trampoline yeah nice trampoline all
right one more
headphones
and then what seems like the hardest
word to rhyme with like just a really
crazy word like amalgamism but not that
what the frick is an algorithm
it doesn't matter but you know a word
like that
i don't know
microphone microphone nice all right so
bed trampoline headphones and microphone
those are the words right
are you ready
let's go
yeah
uh uh yeah come on ah yeah yeah come on
hey hey hey
i don't write it down i'd rather snap
off the head i be killing mc's i'm
putting rappers to bed yeah and y'all
know for these styles i got them
thinking i keep the track warm like it's
covered in the blankets i bring heat
over these beats i'm not discreet i'm
putting rappers to bed i'm laying them
in the sheets hold up i'm about to plug
into the live feed got these rappers all
between the sheets like the eyes lee's i
be going much deeper y'all know i run
with words i said i keep it warm like
blankets or the comforter kick a ill
flow i know that y'all can feel those
rappers be soft like [\h__\h] down
pillows h mac i'm on it y'all know that
they be peeping the free these two here
never sleeping on me yeah the whole
industry i'm shaking it up most rappers
faker than [\h__\h] that's why i'm waking
them up listen i do my thing y'all know
i slam the scene and over tracks i'm
about to bounce just like a trampoline
and y'all know that they love how it
sound and keep y'all protected like
trampoline with net that surrounds it
yeah i keep it bouncing y'all know i
bring them true facts my lyrics is fat
they would probably tear through that
breaking the trampoline going down to
the ground uh i experimentally not bound
to no sound yeah keep it moving y'all
know we be doing it big i make you
bounce like trampolines we were using
some kids yeah all up on it imma let my
anger bust some parents said no
trampoline is too dangerous the kids was
like mom why i just wanna try i wanna
jump i wanna get high and reach for the
sky i wanna be me i wanna be free so
please let me get the trampoline come on
mom please answer me damn it g we gon
take it further when i serve you every
bar i kick is murder got that [\h__\h] y'all
never heard of so turn my vocals up till
we up in the red zone i sound good
through speakers i sound good through
headphones y'all know that i come
through off the top with this stylus
spitting she was like what the [\h__\h] is
an amalgamism h magman in this game i
denominated my bad i'm dropping words
that are way too complicated from
headphone we went to microphone which
got me thinking what are other types of
phones what when i do my thing y'all
know i send rappers to hell from home
bars get directors they connected like a
cell phone matt crawl up in it and y'all
know that i'm about to make you all feel
the flowing wrath imma make head spin
like records on a phonograph so many
rappers in the game is who i'm going
past y'all know that homies trash but
homie blast that be me i got that level
which is mastery i be making moves never
passively uh they know i'm flowing
divine i'll be the role model she be
gripping on the water bottle i'm about
to rip it for my people i'ma leave you
all in ruin i said what she said i said
how are you doing my bad i got the intro
down check the way i'm rhyming i can see
the wall behind you it'd be glittery and
shining yeah hmac i'mma run till i'm
dead shout to the chicken white with the
bun on her head yeah mack imma break it
down y'all know that i'm truly rare
shout to your friend on the side fingers
go through your hair yeah y'all know
i'll be testing them with passion and
when i call out what y'all doing with
your live actions you'll be laughing now
check the way i do perform hold up move
to the side let me see that unicorn hmac
i break it down man i see it in the
background imma keep it real i don't
ever bring the wax down yeah they like
wait how did you find me and how did you
see through me and call out what's
behind me see h man got the boys you
feel until the next day i see through
the [\h__\h] see through it like an
x-ray yeah i do my thing to my lyrics
they cling you got the white finger nail
polish a whole bunch of rings yeah i'ma
get it done i'll make you cover your
mouth i'll make your jaw drop to the
floor y'all together no doubt here i
must kick a freestyle you gonna bug till
the end and when i really blow your mind
i got you hugging your friend you can't
believe it man it's out of control when
i let these lyrics out of my soul y'all
know i'm out on a roll see this is why i
keep it locked on omegle dial see i'm
blessed to have this opportunity to make
y'all smile let's go
you like mentioned everything possible
that was insane oh my god i just my
mouth has been smiling so much
yes that's the goal every time thank you
you didn't youtube or anything yeah
definitely definitely i'll type my
channel in the chat that's talent what
the hell thank you awesome
wow thank you well i hope you have a
nice
time singing i hope you go far with it
thank you
thank you it's a
massive talent thank you guys so much
okay thank you
have a beautiful day all right peace
yo what's up whoa your setup is sick
dude oh thank you i like yours too what
are you up to
uh i i'm vibing before i am before i hop
on down nice the prevalent vibe session
well yo i'm on here i'm doing freestyle
raps for people can i do a freestyle for
you really yeah
so can you give me like three random
crazy words to inspire my freestyle
tacos
a monitor
monitor
coochie
yes all right all right so we got so we
got tacos
monitor and kuchi right yes are you
ready
yeah all right let's go
um
come on hey hey hey hey said that be
coming off the top though improvising
high flows every time i rhyme i got
flavor like tacos about other rappers i
could not know fuss i'm a staple in l.a
like a taco truck yeah killing
instrumentals what i'm always for i got
flavor when i'm rhyming like the alpi
star hmac the main feature when rocking
the theater yeah i leave these rappers
crispy fry like carnitas i'm coming off
the tip bomb with the vocals all these
rappers they be chicken yeah they poyo h
mech i be really going in any
competition if it's rhyming i'm about to
win yeah rappers kind of rocking but not
so well they got them fast food lyrics
word to taco bell hmac when i'm on it
man you know that i transcend through
i'm a five-star restaurant this ain't no
no dollar man you uh yeah and y'all know
i leave them scarred well uh crunchy
tracks kind of like hard shells mac
y'all know that i'll really be the freer
eating wrappers up i fry them just like
a tortilla i be going in up at the top
and kicking the heat flows ooh i got the
game all up on rap like a
burrito i know i'm number one free i
told you i cook up the tortilla but i'm
bout to tell these rappers that they
cheesy quesadilla ooh mac i'm all up on
it i'ma keep it honest get the mic up in
my palm i keep it like a promise yeah
when i'm rhyming hmac be my monika hey
right now you can see me on your monitor
hmac i'm out here live in my dream huh
spit in it clean while i'm live on your
screen y'all know if they don't let me
in then i'll be crashing through the
doorway clean like a monitor when it's
up in 4k hmac y'all know that i'm crazy
y'all can see me vivid like a monitor
with hd more than 1080. matter of fact
i'm 8k matter of fact i'm 16k can't
nobody spit this way back up and go in
and when i come at the top of the mind i
get that shine people lose they
[\h__\h] marbles when i rhyme hard
flows i hit you i'ma paint a picture i
make you think right i be shining like
your pink light check the notion i'm
smoother than the lotion in fact the
light you got they make your ceiling
turn the ocean hmac y'all know rappers
they don't even stand a chance this is
your pre-show vibe before valeran hmac
man i'm slaying them lames we're
devalorant but i ain't playing no games
when i kill the game man y'all know i do
it truly better bet my lyrics be more
wetter than some kochie h mac i'm on it
and i'll be the sickest rhyme i said
they wetter than the coochie they wetter
than the vagina they wetter than [\h__\h]
so you how it should be i get nasty when
they becoming the lyrics i told you can
nobody surpass me ask me for boss i will
deliver we're the coroner but ain't
nobody sick hey yo i'm cutting through
the track like a surgeon shout to valor
in my perspective is first person yeah i
be dope rappers don't have hope hey
we're developing i got these haters in
my scope yeah they get provoked hey i
make you naughty when they becoming
deliveries right now for the time
they'll be calling me god with no facade
i wear no mask up to the task i'm about
to kill i got the skills how do i do it
from the foundation when i build i be
rocking people on omegle living out my
dream you see me on the monitor i'm
rocking on your screen let's go
holy [\h__\h]
no you're actually something else oh
thank you you're actually something like
i didn't expect you to like you had like
so many verses for one word like what
yo thank you
holy crap keep doing this for people
oh thank you so much i appreciate you oh
what's your youtube drop your youtube
yeah hell yeah i'll drop it in the chat
right now i go by harry mack
all right i subscribed oh thank you i
appreciate you you're welcome have a
good night you two have a good valerian
session
thank you peace
bye-bye
yo what's up holy [\h__\h] that camera how
you guys doing
how are you doing i'm doing good i'm
doing good what are you up to nothing
much yeah chilling nice nice where are
you guys at florida florida nice wait
you play piano uh i make beats and stuff
but actually i'm on here i'm doing
freestyle raps for people can i do a
freestyle for you guys oh yeah hey hold
on do one for the troops hey you mind if
we record it absolutely go for it man no
doubt so look here's the thing i i need
your help cause you know i'm gonna
improvise right so let me get like three
random crazy words to inspire my
freestyle [\h__\h] it get get them one bro
this guy is cooking so [\h__\h] i don't
know pasta pasta pasta nice
aura
what is that
that's just like one of our sayings yeah
what does it mean
it's a mating call for marines a mating
call for marines
you say that to them to get little
crayons and crayons
crayons all right let me get one more
let me get one more
mre
yeah like the meal is ready to eat
meals ready to eat is that what that
means
yeah yeah oh that's amazing all right
pasta ura crayons
and mre the meals ready to eat all right
y'all ready
let's have some fun
yeah come on hey yeah come on yeah come
on hey come on hey come on yeah yeah
yeah yeah uh hey yo we ready to ride uh
they can feel it from the bottom the top
hold on we on omegle and we making the
pop anytime i kick hillary people know
that it's hot i said i'm here smoking
microphones something like a roster
eating all my competitors something like
pasta wait i said competitors but i
meant imposters harry mack i'm all up on
it y'all know i'm a rocket i foster a
whole lot of skill inside me yeah i
plugged it right now on the live feed
doing what i'm feeling and i'm living
like a boss called this frostwort the
marinara cause i got the sauce hold up
yeah hmac y'all know i'm out here
flaming treat your mind like pasta and
then i drain it yeah and y'all know
every problem getting solved with words
i'm a brain from the drain something
like a colander wait i said brain from
the drain i meant drained from the brain
i guess i flipped the script these other
rappers hypocrites they talked about it
but i did the [\h__\h] i'm living different
i'm rocking for days your homies walking
away hold up yeah went around they
turned me up loud yeah we went from
three to a two-person crowd either way
you know i blow your mind when i'm
kicking the true flows quickly shift
from a trio to duo i come up the top and
y'all know i'm bout to slam when it
comes to lyricism they know harry mack's
the man and i'm doing this for all of
y'all my bars sounding too rough when
i'm spitting they'd be yelling now
hmac man these rappers don't create it
all basically for marines that is like a
mate and call this every mack
know what y'all saying they like it's
one of us saying so i'm coming right off
the tip of this i'm about to slam i'm
the man and i'm blending different
colors like some crayons from crayola
rappers only get their records played
through payola the illest off the tip i
thought i [\h__\h] told ya yeah
y'all know they know eventually hey yo
they dropped the three letters the mre
yeah y'all know i get loose up on the
beat eating instrumentals so i guess my
meal's ready to eat yeah it's hmac man
y'all know i always been the guy my
name's max so uh max really energized
yeah i'ma re-spell your whole acronym
people get their minds blown every time
i rap for them yeah and y'all know i'm
here to do it bring the remedy cause my
music radiates energy yeah and i'm here
to make it happen it's hvac i'm in the
mix i really get it cracking got the
lyrics right over the top of the mental
detector they couldn't compute yeah when
i hopped on he was like do one for the
troops so i'm giving y'all the scoop i'm
loaded up with the ammo peace to the
truth with the caps on and the camo yeah
i got you trembling lyrical just like
eminem but then again no camo cause the
mac ain't blending in hey yo i'm
standing out like a highlighter i use
the forest like i'm flying in the tie
fighter i'm here for all of y'all i'm
off the top you know i'm scorching you i
got love for the homies rapping out of
florida hmac y'all know i spit deadly
off the brain hold me in the bucket have
my bars as heavy as your chain let's go
yeah
[\h__\h] hey
that was the tightest puff hell yeah
thank you man yo you got like spotify or
anything like that definitely man i go
by harry mack i actually i'm biggest on
youtube so i'll type that in the chat
it's just youtube.com harry mack
that was tight as [\h__\h] i guess you
probably got two more new subscribers
hey let's go i appreciate that so much
thank you guys
y'all enjoy the rest of your night all
right all right bro peace out
what's going on people first and
foremost i just have to say thank you i
cannot believe we're already here at the
50th episode of the amigo bar series it
has been an insane journey fun fact it's
almost been one year since we posted the
first episode of amigo bars next week
we're going to hit that one year
anniversary so there's definitely a lot
to celebrate and i have just been
completely blown away by the level of
support this series has received so to
everyone who's been watching the videos
liking the videos commenting their
favorite bars favorite reactions to
everyone that's on my channel at 8 59
a.m pacific time every friday just
refreshing refreshing waiting for that
amigo bars drop this one is for y'all
couple big announcements first of all we
are making some changes to the schedule
we are no longer going to be dropping
amigo bars every friday now wait before
you freak out we are not stopping the
amigo bar series not at all we're just
not going to be posting amigo bars every
friday so there's four fridays in the
month except for some weird months that
randomly have five fridays which blows
my mind but in any case we're gonna be
shuffling through different types of
content each friday so one friday might
be amigo bars one friday might be a vlog
episode one friday might be guerrilla
whoa whoa whoa whoa said a little bit
too much right there
uh look just know we have a ton of dope
content coming to y'all in the next few
months and i'm super excited for you to
see it announcement number two y'all
have been asking for it for a long time
and it's finally here the top 50 omegle
bars performances in audio form as a two
volume set on spotify apple music title
amazon music wherever you stream your
music it's there right now
click the link in the description go run
those streams up let's get some of these
amigo bar freestyles over a million
streams on spotify how crazy would that
be we have the opportunity to flip the
whole industry on its head with this
project and i'm super excited for y'all
to hear it without further ado let's get
back to the episode
yo what's up hey
how's it going pretty good you're good
nice what are you up to
we're just on a mega because we're bored
oh yeah yeah well hey maybe i can help
cure your boredom i'm on here doing
freestyle raps for people can i do one
for you
yes
amazing amazing okay cool so um i need
your help though cause i'm gonna
improvise my lyrics so can i get like
three crazy random kind of like
challenging words you know to inspire my
rap
um
[Music]
sushi
sushi yet nice
brownies brownies
sad face yeah non-food now good call
um
softball
all right let's get it sushi brownie and
softball you ready
yo
uh i'ma blow your mind truly when it
comes to lyrics mine are raw like sushi
yeah and all these other rappers getting
dissed you better bet that all my flows
is wetter than some fish sharing mac i'm
all up in it i'm taking full control all
these lyrics that i kicked they coming
from the soul i'm the illest off the top
i think you want to know and shouts out
to sushi cause you know i'm on a roll
matt call up in it you know that it
might be rumors but i'm pretty sure his
flow is hotter than the spicy tuna yeah
every time i rhyme i'm about to own your
soul i'm a classic kinda like the
california roll uh and y'all know i
drive him straight mad yeah rap is
imitation like that fake crab but hmac
man you know i'm bout to win uh i'll be
massive y'all i'm the opposite of a
shrimp hold up y'all can't see me put my
words together cleanly matter of fact
that tastes fresh like you eating some
sashimi
and when they hear me rhyme they know
this boy's boss hey yo my enemies is
salty word to soy sauce hey yo i'm next
level y'all know how i'm ripping i'm
flipping i got the sushi soy sauce
dipping i got the added flavor i'm major
i shock like taser i'm precious like a
laser beam living my dream with lyrical
scheme like you've never seen came to
bury rhymers they can feel me all the
way in north carolina i'm off the top of
this forever and my sound beat free plus
on beats i'm sweet like a brownie h mac
got the lyrics y'all can catch fresh
about the oven with the brownie wrap
batch yeah and when i grip the mic i'm
about to let it roll for my freestyle
versus your brownies is the metaphor why
cause they coming out fresh from the
oven with the vibe that you loving and
y'all know that i'm related to the track
like it's my cousin and these rappers
claim they high up in the sky but they
still can't deny no one's above them yet
i'm here for y'all i'mma rock till i'm
dead shout the girl with the necklace
who be nod in the head yeah i'm doing
this for both of y'all i'mma roast them
all i hop on omegle i had to kick some
clothes for y'all sushi brownie we
making the moves for the third word they
was like please no food hmac imma do it
yo i come through hot what was the third
word you said i already forgot
[Music]
oh i'm a boss y'all i'm bout to knock it
out the park like softball hmac man i
really leave them scar job but then
again if i'm rapping i'm playing
hardball hey yo i'm nice with the words
y'all i serve y'all unpredictable with
the lyrics i throw a curveball check the
style make you say wow i do it now chip
the ball hit it off to the side my
lyrics fell yeah and y'all know i
believe you in amazement like we playing
softball knock it out the park sliding
to bases yo i'm here to hit the home run
here to hit the grand slam every time
i'm on the mic you know i drop an anthem
doing what i'm feeling and i leave y'all
in amazement peace to my two new friends
rocking the braces hmac y'all know that
i'm bout to kick a beast rhyme when i
call em out they'd be throwing up the
peace signs yeah yo i don't play with
the verse i see the red letters yo but
what's it say on your shirt let me read
that real quick so i can drop it in the
lyric every time i kick a lyric it
emanates from the spirit now listen when
i'm live upon the track i'mma flame it
up fans go crazy from mac like
beatlemania y'all know i'm bout to blow
your mind with the verse big love to the
most famous band on the earth cause i
bring the rhythm when i bring those bars
i said i bring the rhythm like i'm ringo
starr hmac i'm transcending the bars i'm
about to bend them one of the illest
songwriters like i'm john lennon hmac
they think they on my level i say hardly
i'd be innovating like my name paul
mccartney mac off the top of this you
know i got to do my thing word to george
harrison these rappers are embarrassing
cause when i do my thing you know i love
the scene going deep kind of like a
yellow submarine hmac when i'm in it man
y'all know i gotta throw it down king
with the freestyle [\h__\h] rocking the
golden crown what
whoa
that was sick that was
amazing
thank you amazing
thank you thank you
really sick
one of the coolest people we've seen oh
i'm honored i'm honored thank you
hope you have a good day yes same to you
peace
i'm not yo what's up hi
how's it going
i'm good you have good quality oh thank
you appreciate it yo can i do a
freestyle rap for you guys can't do it
all right i need your help let me get
three random words to inspire my
freestyle and they need to be
challenging not basic words like dog and
cat you know like like complicated words
no yoda yoda nice
waterfall waterfall
intersection intersection
yoda
waterfall and intersection you ready
wait wait wait i want a video and then
we record yeah yeah go ahead any tv show
i don't know
yoda waterfall intersection let's get it
you ready
yes all right
yeah
yeah yeah come on want to listen ah come
on juan cho listen uh yeah yeah i'm
about to glow up i got something real to
show ya every time i rap i'm dropping
facts like yoda i got the lyrics that
they begging for i'm about to take y'all
on a trip out to dagger
hmac when i'm rapping yo they call me a
guard i use the force to lift the x-wing
out of the bog yeah and y'all know i'm
bout to spit so fly like yoda said do or
do not there is no try my flow is vital
this here is the old school revival
something like baby yoda mac is going
viral seen around the planet with these
rapping reports your career like baby
yoda cause it's coming up short listen
hey yo tell me what it mean to me i used
to smoke on yo the skin that's the
greenery yeah nowadays i stopped cause
it made me too paranoid that's the [\h__\h]
that i avoid now i'm making hella noise
mac i'm up in it i'm ready to score
chess of course fancy like i was ripping
the poor shots of the yoda i'm using the
force yeah all of the lyrics i'm kicking
y'all know that they more dope i said
i'm killing you dead like vader with the
force choke i strangle them i'm angling
my lyrics just a bang again hanging
friends off the edge of the cliff get
you lifted like a spliff yeah find
another rapper who could bust this [\h__\h]
like this hold up i'm bout to drop it in
they know i'm bout to ride for them
forever i'm coming with the bars that
are clever hmac the people want to see
me flow she goes hold up are we gonna be
on a tv show like dog what is this i'mma
let like everybody witness cause when i
spit this i work it out like fitness i'm
here for all of y'all they call mac his
majesty i know the word you really
wanted though it was tapestry yeah i'm
bout to kill it y'all can picture that i
was listening close i even heard you
whisper that yeah hmac microphones is
what i've been just wrecking hey yo i'm
meeting with these rappers at the
intersection yeah check it when i spit
i'd be a bars where's the streets that
be intersecting rappers got me crossed i
don't take no laws y'all know i'm bout
to spit it free hold up let me adjust
the intersection now it's a t well i'm
about to leave you rappers t-boned when
i crash and cause collision y'all know
that these poems is often hitting hey yo
i'll never stop and not for a second i'm
great i eat y'all off the plate like
t-bone steak hey yo i'm here for all of
y'all kicking the lyrics this strong
piece of both of these girls with the
hair that is blonde yeah y'all know when
i'm spitting man i'm really bout to
wreck absurd i got yoda and intersection
what was the second word please remind
me
[Music]
oh waterfall okay wait i got you all
every time i grab the mic you know a
bodybuilder i be flowing like a
waterfall compare me to niagara hmac
it's never written rappers must be
kidding i be spitting like a waterfall
all my saliva is hitting from every
angle y'all know you better bet i get it
wetter than water when falling they know
my flow is appalling yeah waterfall
clashing way above the average like
white water and waterfalls my rate is
rapping on it's hmac y'all know i'm
living my dream ah where the waterfalls
i'm sending rappers upstream they up
shit's creek no paddle they don't really
want to battle with the way that i
deliver man about to give y'all shivers
on the waterfall from river cause i go
from top to bottom then i grow from
bottom back to top and keep it rocking
often i'm on yeah came through off the
top and i'mma rip freeze the tapestry up
in your background hella trippy hey yo i
grip up on the mic and leave you floor
they was like
wait wait a minute let us record now
they pulling out their phones ah y'all
know i'ma rock the world peace to the
girl with the necklace that is made of
pearls yeah y'all know that i really be
the man i'm a slam shining like the
pearl that's coming out the clam yeah h
mac man y'all know that i slammed well
all my bars hard they'd be just like a
clam shell hmac i blow your mind with
thunder refreeze feeling like a clan
that be living under the sea i'm
speaking like this i never sounded weak
i'm legit hey yo i'm about to take you
to the peak of this [\h__\h] yeah matt call
upon it and y'all know i make them true
moves no it's not a tv show but y'all
gonna be on youtube what
oh
god
thank you wow you're welcome okay that
was insane like how did you just like
come up with all this
yeah yeah i've been practicing for a
long time you know that is so good
that you're going to get really far
thank you thank you so much i appreciate
it
you're welcome welcome yo so i'm
actually i'm making videos for my
youtube channel right now would you guys
be cool with me using this clip in one
of my videos
yeah yeah amazing amazing i'll drop my
youtube channel in the chat just so you
have it all right appreciate you guys
thanks for being a part of it you're
welcome all right
a million
yeah that's me
congrats you deserve it thank you so
much appreciate it bye
bye-bye peace out great day thanks you
too
what's up man
what's up
how you doing
i'm doing good how are you i'm doing
really good man you know i just can't
complain that's cool that's cool uh well
yo what what are you up to man
i'm just
yo i'm just chilling you know what i'm
saying i'm just just
just talking to people just chilling
talking to people that's dope well yo
can i do a freestyle rap for you
yeah you got it but you got to help me
out man because i'm going to improvise
you know so i need like three
random challenging words to inspire
every story all right all right
icicle yeah nice that's great icicles
um two more
senseless senseless nice yes and
emotional emotional
icicle
senseless
and emotional yeah those three right
there are you ready
yes hey yeah check it out come on hey
come on check it out come on yeah yeah
yeah yo
uh check out how nice i flow dripping
off the tip like a icicle it's senseless
to step cause i'm dope with flows uh yo
these beats got me emotional hold up i
said check out how nice i flow i be
dripping off the tip like a icicle it's
senseless to step i got the dopest flows
yeah instrumentals making me emotional
hold up i'll be the rapper that's chosen
i really goes and i be leaving
instrumentals like icicles leave them
frozen i'm coming right off the top and
i'm leaving all these tracks injured
matter of fact i'm dripping like the ice
it cools up in the winter i'm here yeah
y'all know that they really about to
mention bruh i'm something like the
winter wind i will reduce your
temperature yeah i got it down to like
zero that be celsius and when it comes
to cold lyrics can't nobody tell me [\h__\h]
yeah like a icicle that's melting quick
that's how i be dripping off the tongue
though yeah i be throwing mad length to
my verses like the hair of rapunzel
meg y'all know that i'm out here having
fun bro i'm doing what i'm feeling and
y'all know i'm bout to win uh y'all know
i'm about to make you niger head again
yeah hmac everything i say is rare shout
to the homie and the backwards cap in
the game and chair yeah i'ma break it
down y'all know that my flow's amazing
he be repping gt racing yeah i'll be on
it just to break it down i'll blow you
down when i kick the sacred sound yeah
check the way it sounds listen peep out
how nice i flow dripping off the tip
like a icicle it's senseless to step i'm
the dopest bro uh these checks making me
emotional hold up i said peep how nice i
flow i be dripping off the tip just like
a icicle it's senseless to step i'm the
dopest yo chag's making me emotional now
check it out y'all know i'm ill and i'm
spilling from the second i'm in the
building i'm murdering mcs but this
ain't no senseless killing i gotta
murder them and i'm about to change your
senses it's every mecca be the illest
that be the consensus yeah and y'all
know i live my purpose and my vision i
can feel it in my senses it's all up in
my nervous system i'm doing well i'm
here to excel speaking the senses my
bars got the funkiest smell speaking of
senses people love the way that it
sounds you can taste it when i'm
spitting and i'm spraying it now yeah
hey yo y'all know i got the best taste
with bars i'm lazed with bars i'm up in
the place i'm hard i try to tell you i'm
bout to leave the facial scarred if i
have to and in the obstacle they build
up that's what i blast through it's the
mag dude to attack you is that true yes
indeed y'all know i'mma bless em sees i
cook up the recipe kinda like dr dre and
kendrick did y'all know when i rhymed
about to mention this i'm stupendous
with the lyrics rappers i might laugh at
y'all shout out to the homie with the
cap on and the shirt for basketball yeah
i'm here i leave a field of dead clones
my vocals in the red zone you got the
mic and headphone attachment i'm rapping
you about to know me soon what you
eating ice cream or cereal off the spoon
yeah i work a miracle forever i be on a
rapping grand imperial bar spit is the
hard hitter the one that's about to let
y'all know how it's done bring it back
to the hook while i shine with the sun i
hold up they peeping out how nice i flow
i'm dripping off the mental like a
icicle it's senseless to step i'm the
dopest bro all these tracks make me
emotional hold up hold up i said check
out how nice i flow i'm dripping off the
tip just like a icicle it's senseless to
step i'm the dopest bro one more verse
we're gonna hit them like this check it
check it
when i'm killing y'all know i be one in
a million i got rappers emotional they
deep up in their feelings yeah and y'all
know that they really want this bad uh
got these rappers mad emotional they
hella sad listen uh and the vape that's
how you coping you puffing on the vape
pen to deal with your emotions yeah i
understand that y'all i am the nicest i
will entice quick and all of us have
vices don't trust anyone who claims that
they doesn't yeah i used to smoke the
cannabis to keep me buzzing yeah i used
to drink a lot of liquor out the cup
yeah but i got damn near giving up so i
had to quit the stuff now i'm focused on
the bars i'll be locked in on omegle and
i'm really going hard sharp like an
icicle for the senseless rap killing got
you emotional and deep up in your
feelings let's go that [\h__\h] was fire
that [\h__\h] was fire that was crazy thank
you crazy you got to youtube i do yep
yep yep i'll type it in the chat i go by
harry mack so it's just
youtube.com harry mack
harry mack
yes sir oh so you crazy oh so you're
crazy yeah yeah yeah
oh my god geez that was fire thank you
man
oh my god
nah
that's crazy thank you bro that's crazy
that's crazy what's up guys really hope
you enjoyed the episode if you did
please remember to like comment
subscribe to the channel and if you are
a fan of the amigo bar series definitely
make sure you check out my patreon over
here we are now releasing amigo outtakes
on the patreon feed this is exclusive
bonus material from the amigo series
that isn't going to exist anywhere else
check it out